planetc.net 2018-02-16

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy on Personal Information (‘Policy’) supersedes all existing polices on the subject matter.

This Policy applies to all Personal Data collected electronically by Essel Shyam Communication Limited, its subsidiary(ies), affiliates and group companies (“Company).

The Company is sensitive about privacy issues on the Internet and takes seriously the trust you place in us. In general, you can visit Company’s websites without telling us who you are and without revealing any information about yourself. There are times, however, when we may need information from you. There are times, however, when we may collect/need information from you. At the time of collection of such information the Company may try (without any obligation) to inform you about the collection of information.

You may choose to give us personal information such as your name and address or e-mail identification address (‘ID’) that may be needed, for example, to correspond with you, for you to download our white papers, to provide you with subscription information etc. You recognize and understand that there is no compulsion on you to provide us with your personal information and any and all personal information provided by you to us is with your full consent, own volition and desire to provide such personal information. However, Company will not be liable to any unsolicited information provided by you. You consent and authorize the Company using such information as per it’s privacy policy. We intend to protect the quality and integrity of your personally identifiable information.

Information is also collected to measure the number of visits, average time spent on the website, pages viewed, etc. is used to measure the use of our website and to improve the content of the website.

If you register with one of Company’s business units online, they may use this information to provide you with custom information about Company’s offering in support of your business needs. A technology called cookies may be used to provide you with tailored information. A cookie is a tiny element of data that a website can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your hard drive so we can recognize you when you return. You may set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie. Registering with any Company business unit online signifies your unconditional consent to receive such cookies.

#### Company will take reasonable steps to ensure that all dealings in Personal Data, shall:

  * Be processed fairly & lawfully;
  * Be obtained only with the consent of the information provider;
  * Be collected, only when: 
    * The information is collected for a lawful purpose connected with a function or activity of Company; and
    * The collection of the sensitive personal data or information is considered necessary for that purpose.
  * Be available for review by the information provider, as and when requested.
  * Be kept secure against unauthorized or unlawful processing and against accidental loss, destruction or damage, as per the prescribed standards.

To prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, to maintain data accuracy and to ensure the appropriate use of the information, Company utilizes appropriate physical, technical and administrative procedures to safeguard the information we collect.

At times we conduct online surveys to better understand the needs and profiles of our visitors. When we conduct a survey, we will try (but are not obligated) to let you know how we will use the information at the time we collect information from you on the Internet.

Company does not share personal information about you with non-affiliated companies except: (a) to provide products or services you’ve requested; (b) when we have your permission: or (c) under the following circumstances:

#### Company will take reasonable steps to ensure that all dealings in Personal Data, shall:

  * We provide the information to trusted entities who work on behalf of or with Company under strict confidentiality agreements. These entities may use your personal information to help Company communicate with you about offers from Company and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to further share or disseminate this information;
  * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;
  * We believe it is necessary to share the information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action against any illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, or as otherwise required by law.
  * We believe it is necessary to share the information in order to protect or enforce Company’s rights, usage terms, intellectual or physical property or for safety of Company or associated parties.
  * We may share information about you if Company is acquired by or merged with another company.

We will make a sincere effort to respond in a timely manner to your requests to correct inaccuracies in your personal information. To correct inaccuracies in your personal information, please return the message containing the inaccuracies to the sender. Company’s websites are not directed at nor targeted at children. No one who has not reached the age of thirteen may use the websites unless supervised by an adult.

Company may provide links to third-party websites for your convenience and information. If you access those links through the Company website, you will leave the Company’s website. Company does not control those sites or their privacy practices, which may differ from Company’s practices. We do not endorse or make any representations about third-party websites. The personal data you choose to provide to or that is collected by these third parties, including any social media websites featured on our website, is not covered by the Company Privacy Policy. We encourage you to review the privacy policy of any website before submitting your personal information.

We may also provide social media features on our website that enable you to share Company information with your social networks and to interact with Company on various social media sites. Your use of these features may result in the collection or sharing of information about you, depending on the feature. We encourage you to review the privacy policies and settings on the social media sites with which you interact to make sure you understand the information that could be shared by those sites.

Company may transfer your personal information to any other body corporate or a person in any country that ensures the “same level of data protection” that is adhered to by it. Company shall also not publish your personal information and shall ensure that the information transferred to a third party is not further disclosed by it. Company respects your privacy considerations and hence provides an option to you, to not provide the data or information sought to be collected. Further, you can also withdraw your consent which was earlier given to Company, and the same must be communicated to Company in writing. Company shall not be responsible for the authenticity of the Personal Data supplied to it by the provider, whose duty it is to ensure that the information provided by it or its employees is authentic.

Any grievance or complaint, in relation to processing of information, should be sent to Company in writing to following contact email ID. Grievance shall be redressed as expeditiously as possible. Email ID _____________

Please note that this Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Policy without your explicit consent. We will post any Policy changes on this page. We will also keep prior versions of this Policy in an archive for your review.
